the last video in my story was published
a couple days ago and after seeing the
15 stories lined out including the
conclusion I realized there was one
glaring omission and of course it was
the one I omitted and that is my
addictions I am not like other addiction
stories because I'm not sober I'm not
even trying to get sober my addictions
are things that I want to have in my
life I want to find a balance with them
my two addictions are media both social
media and movies and TV shows as well as
marijuana they're both used to dumb me
oh and they're both used as
entertainment and they both are sources
of thought and ideas and a way to
procrastinate from taking steps forward
I have been with both of these
addictions for a very long time and I
have seen that the method I'm using to
approach them is working because one the
addictions have less hold of my life
than they ever they used to and I'm
happier I don't have the same shame and
guilt I did it's still there there's
still some that's why this video didn't
get may that's why I didn't even occur
to me to make it during that the lay you
know my other my other stories I it's a
weird one in society I'm both it's the
one place I don't yet fully love and
accept myself I'm getting there but I'm
not there yet and it's one place that
society definitely doesn't love and
accept people in we accept some people's
addictions we accept addictions to money
and power we don't accept addictions to
substances and even social media I would
not say for it's it's so commonplace
that we're okay with it but we
definitely talk about it's a negative
thing
and it probably is I am living my life
with authenticity so I've been given the
guidance from my internal guides I still
had to figure out what better word for
them
my intuition my subconscious whatever
the I wrote of these whatever the
messages come from that I either need to
give up my addictions or I just need to
own them I need to be honest and
transparent about where they are
constantly and that's kind of too many
things to be transparent on every
bidding I'm not gonna move I'm not gonna
update you on my health and my
challenges and where my brains at and
where my addictions are at and what I
did good that day and when I did bad
that day I'm sure I will do that but I
can't do all of that in every video but
nor am i hiding it I smoke pot daily I
go through small periods of not smoking
it for a while when the need calls when
I know there is when I feel the Colleen
when it's like yep time to give it up
for a while until it's then time to use
it for a while pot and media have both
been great fuel for my ideas and also
hindrances to them and so my journey is
finding the balance neither of them do I
want to give up completely I don't want
to never watch TV shows and movies I
like them and I don't want to the irony
I don't know it's ironic the beautiful
thing is that as I've gone through this
process this journey of learning to love
and accept myself including where I am
in my addictions they've both loosened
their grip on my life I am less addicted
to them than I was six months or a year
ago or two years ago each time I go
through a cycle of getting more down the
rabbit hole in the back out the rabbit
hole each time has less and less grip on
my life and it would feel like I was
doing it for society to cancel it out
completely
and I don't think abstinence for me is
the answer it is to follow this journey
and showcase it and be authentic in it
and I just wanted to honor that the
addiction story is absolutely a part of
my story in the past and ongoing and
just like my health challenges just like
a lot of what I have that I've went
through I also honor that my addiction
is a baby addiction compared to other
peoples I can go off a bit for a couple
weeks it's hard I have to deal with
willpower and I have very little little
power when it comes to things certain
things but I've done it I don't spend
our rent money on it I don't my kid
isn't neglected and gonna be taken away
by by Child Protective Services at any
point in time it's not it's not as
devastating as an of an addiction as
other people's who really do truly need
to cut it out of their life because it
has a devastating impact on them their
health their family mine is safe enough
to stay it gives me something and it
costs me something and it's my journey
and my job not anybody else is to find
that balance and because I'm choosing to
it's also my job to share that journey
as a piece of my overall journey in this
life so this is my addiction video thank
you